nasba.org 2011-12-03

# NASBA.org Privacy Policy Last updated: August 2, 2011

                                    NASBA.org Privacy Policy
                                  Last updated: August 2, 2011
At NASBA, we recognize the importance of privacy and how crucial it is to protect the privacy of
all who use our products and services. This Privacy Policy pertains to all the products and
services offered by NASBA through its website at www.nasba.org (herein referred to as
nasba.org), and its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. This policy will tell you what information
is collected by nasba.org, how it is protected, how we use it and what choices you have about
how the information is used.
What do we collect?
Nasba.org collects personally identifiable information about users only when the user voluntarily
provides such information. For some of our sites you must set up a user profile, and that will
require specific information about you. This information may include name, address, telephone
number(s), email address, date of birth, license number(s), license expiration date(s) and
payment information. Once this information is received, reasonable measures are maintained
throughout processing to guard the privacy and security of your personal information.
Nasba.org collects non-personal identification information through the use of cookies and/or
Internet Protocol (IP) address tracking. Cookies are small text files stored on your computer
when you initially visit a website that make your browser unique to that site. We use cookies to
recognize if you have been to our sites before, making your ongoing access and usage of the
sites easier and smoother. Information is also gathered about the areas you visit on our sites
and about the links to other sites on the Internet you may click from within our sites. However,
nasba.org is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We
encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements
of each website we are linked to that may collect personally identifiable information.
NASBA is not responsible for the nature, quality or accuracy of the content or opinions
expressed on sites we do not control or monitor. Consult the privacy policies of these sites
before providing any personal information.
How we use (and don’t use) your email
When you utilize any services available through nasba.org, we store the email address in the
event further correspondence is needed. We do not share or sell your email address or any
other personal information that would aid in creating unsolicited emails or other materials.
No liability for acts of third parties
Although we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of all personal and non-
personal information, transmissions made via the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure.
Nasba.org will have no liability for disclosure of information due to errors in transmission or
unauthorized acts of third parties.

Confidentiality
NASBA reserves the right to disclose to third parties information about usage of our sites and
any related services, including information gathered during your use of nasba.org. Any
information disclosed will be in the form of aggregate data (such as overall patterns or
demographic reports) that does not describe or identify any individual user.
We will not disclose personal information to any third party without your express permission,
except in the following limited circumstances, in which we will consider, and may release to third
parties:
    1. To comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant,
         subpoena or court order;
    2. In special cases, such as to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities,
         suspected fraud or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any
         person.
Legal disclosure of information
NASBA may disclose personally identifiable information if we are required to do so by law, or we
in good faith believe that such action is necessary to:
    1. Comply with the law or the legal process,
    2. Protect and defend our rights and property,
    3. Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our sites, or
    4. Protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.
* Please note that we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
Lost or stolen information
If your credit card or password is stolen or used without your permission from any of our sites,
immediately notify your card provider in accordance with its rules and procedures, and contact
NASBA. Upon notification, NASBA will cancel any false transactions and compromised
passwords, and will update any affected records.
Security
NASBA uses reasonable precautions to protect information about our customers while it is
stored on our servers or in transit to our vendors processing on our behalf. Sensitive information
that is transmitted to us online (such as a credit card number) is encrypted and is transmitted to
us securely, using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption. In addition, access to all of our
customers' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. Only
employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, an application
processor or candidate service associate) are granted access to personally identifiable

information. Finally, the servers on which we process personally identifiable information are kept
in a safe and secure environment.
Accessing and correcting personal information/Opt out
You have a right to know about the personal information NASBA has collected through your
requests as described above, including the right to correct, amend or delete the information we
have on file if it is incorrect. You may also change the status of whether you wish to receive
alerts, newsletters and communications at any time. If you wish to exercise these rights, feel
free to contact us at by calling (615) 880-4200. You may still receive emails containing important
or relevant information about your account.
Your California privacy rights
Beginning January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that
are California residents to request that we not share your personal information with third parties
for their direct marketing for personal, household or family use.
Governing law
Nasba.org is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. By using
this site, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with this
Policy, please do not disclose any personal information through this site. This Policy and the
use of this site are governed by Tennessee law. Users of this site consent to the jurisdiction and
venue of such courts as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes
concerning this Policy. This Policy and the notices outlined herein are not intended to and do
not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any third party. Any claim
related to the site or this Policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in Davidson County,
Nashville, Tennessee, within one year after the claim arises.
Children
Our site is not directed at individuals less than 13 years of age and we do not intend to collect
any personally identifiable information from such individuals.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
NASBA reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any of our governing
Privacy Policies at any time. You are responsible for reviewing this Policy periodically, and your
continued use of our sites following changes to the policies will be considered acceptance of
any changes. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the site.
Contact us
NASBA welcomes comments and questions about this Policy and about nasba.org. Feel free to
contact us at by calling (615) 880-4200 for any questions or comments you have.
